yhyouxi.net 2015-04-26

# privacy - yhyouxi play free online games

## Privacy

* * *

At www.yhyouxi.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.yhyouxi.net and how it is used. 

We will notify you if we change this privacy policy. 

#### Registration:

When you create an account we request to enter your nickname, email, gender, birth date and country.

At this time we are not displaying any of the details above. but in most cases nickname and gender are displayed to public, the rest are displayed by user choice. 

#### Email privacy:

We will **NOT** share, sell, give, display or show your email to any one under any case.  
We will **NOT** send you spam messages.  
We may just send a single message contains some updates to you every month, and we will give you the option to cancel it. 

#### Log Files:

Like many other Web sites, www.yhyouxi.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

#### DoubleClick DART cookie:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   
**Helpful links:**  
Google ad and content network privacy policy  
Network Advertising Initiative 

#### Cookies and Web Beacons:

We may use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site . Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.yhyouxi.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.yhyouxi.net privacy policy does not apply to, and we cann't control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser's respective websites. 

You can contact us at
